Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم الإدارة، شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
=Phoenix's Homecoming=
=عودة فينيكس إلى الوطن=
=Episode 15=
=الحلقة 15=
Are you trying to turn my imperial study
هل تحاول تحويل مكتبي الإمبراطوري؟
into a football field?
في ملعب كرة قدم؟
I miss you, Your Majesty.
أفتقدك يا ​​جلالة الملك.
I just wanted to see you.
أردت فقط رؤيتك.
Is that wrong?
هل هذا خطأ؟
Where is Yunfei?
أين هو يونفي؟
I sent someone to check on her, but she wouldn't open the door.
أرسلت شخصًا للاطمئنان عليها، لكنها لم تفتح الباب.
Get to the point.
ادخل في صلب الموضوع.
Emperors from the Chen family
أباطرة من عائلة تشين
are all the same, after all.
في النهاية، كلها متشابهة.
You're all obsessed with your sisters
أنتم جميعاً مهووسون بأخواتكم
and crave substitutes.
ويتوقون إلى البدائل.
But honestly, Lady Yunfei appeared out of nowhere.
لكن بصراحة، ظهرت السيدة يونفي من العدم.
Your Majesty,
جلالة الملك،
don't you find it suspicious?
ألا تجد ذلك مثيراً للريبة؟
If you can't watch your tongue,
إذا لم تستطع ضبط لسانك،
I won't hesitate to make you a mute.
لن أتردد في جعلك أبكم.
Yunlin wasn't my sister by blood.
يونلين لم تكن أختي بالدم.
Had she wanted to be the empress,
لو كانت ترغب في أن تصبح إمبراطورة،
no one could have stopped her,
لم يكن بإمكان أحد أن يوقفها،
and I wouldn't have married you.
وما كنت لأتزوجك.
I see Your Majesty
أرى جلالتكم
is quite taken with Lady Yunfei.
معجبة جداً بالسيدة يونفي.
What a pity that such a beauty
يا للأسف أن مثل هذا الجمال
is already engaged.
مخطوبة بالفعل.
It's none of your business.
هذا ليس من شأنك.
Seeing her face,
عندما رأيت وجهها،
Your Majesty,
جلالة الملك،
your mind must be
يجب أن يكون عقلك
racing with thoughts.
تتسابق الأفكار.
I know Your Majesty
أعرف جلالتكم
hasn't let go of the Grand Princess.
لم يتخلوا عن الأميرة الكبرى.
So you've been planning
إذن كنت تخطط
to keep Lady Yunfei
للحفاظ على السيدة يونفي
by your side.
بجانبك.
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
Reluctant as I am,
على الرغم من ترددي،
I will help fulfill your desire
سأساعدك في تحقيق رغبتك
and mend your regrets.
وتخلص من ندمك.
I've been alone in Zhuozhou for so long.
لقد بقيت وحيداً في تشوتشو لفترة طويلة.
I wrote you 26 letters in total.
لقد كتبت لك 26 رسالة في المجموع.
Yet Your Highness only
ومع ذلك، يا صاحب السمو فقط
sent one reply.
تم إرسال رد واحد.
The dignified Grand Tutor,
المعلم الأكبر الجليل،
only after a few days,
بعد بضعة أيام فقط،
has started writing nonsensical letters.
بدأ بكتابة رسائل لا معنى لها.
Now you can't even
الآن لا يمكنك حتى
watch your tongue.
احذر من لسانك.
Heaven bears witness.
السماء تشهد على ذلك.
Every word I say is true.
كل كلمة أقولها هي الحقيقة.
Day and night,
ليلاً ونهاراً،
I yearn for Your Highness alone.
إنني أتوق إلى سموكم وحده.
Zhuozhou is freezing.
تشوتشو متجمدة.
I hold onto your letters for warmth to sleep every night.
أتمسك برسائلك لأشعر بالدفء وأنام كل ليلة.
You should've burned them.
كان عليك حرقهم.
You've overstepped.
لقد تجاوزت حدودك.
There are people...
هناك أناس...
I learned a trick in Zhuozhou.
لقد تعلمت حيلة في تشوتشو.
Just interlock our fingers.
فلنشبك أصابعنا فقط.
And our voices won't carry beyond these walls.
ولن تصل أصواتنا إلى ما وراء هذه الجدران.
Why not just sew your mouth shut?
لماذا لا تقوم ببساطة بخياطة فمك؟
I couldn't.
لم أستطع.
If I sewed my mouth shut,
لو خيطت فمي،
how could I express my feelings for Your Highness?
كيف لي أن أعبر عن مشاعري تجاه سموكم؟
You have plenty of other ways.
لديك العديد من الطرق الأخرى.
With your mouth shut,
أغلق فمك،
you could still do it with your hands and eyes.
لا يزال بإمكانك القيام بذلك بيديك وعينيك.
So you're saying
إذن أنت تقول
that my feelings
تلك هي مشاعري
are perfectly clear to Your Highness.
وهي واضحة تماماً لصاحب السمو.
Don't forget.
لا تنسى.
You're merely my pawn.
أنت مجرد بيدق في يدي.
Do not overstep.
لا تتجاوز الخط.
(Your Highness.)
(صاحب السمو)
(Since you're using me,)
(بما أنك تستغلني،)
(why not use me more thoroughly?)
(لماذا لا تستخدمني بشكل أكثر شمولاً؟)
Your Majesty has been busy.
لقد كان جلالتكم مشغولاً.
Why don't you rest early?
لماذا لا تستريح مبكراً؟
I'll pay my respects to you tomorrow.
سأقدم لك واجب العزاء غداً.
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
I'm afraid I've overstayed my welcome.
أخشى أنني أطلت البقاء.
I'd rather go home soon.
أفضّل العودة إلى المنزل قريباً.
Why is that?
لماذا هذا؟
Because of the empress?
بسبب الإمبراطورة؟
I promise
أعدك
she won't dare approach you again.
لن تجرؤ على الاقتراب منك مرة أخرى.
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
Somebody.
شخص ما.
Pass on my decree.
انقلوا قراري.
If the empress trespasses on the imperial study again,
إذا تعدت الإمبراطورة على مكتبها الإمبراطوري مرة أخرى،
I'll remove her from her position.
سأعزلها من منصبها.
Understood.
مفهوم.
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
I shall take my leave.
سأغادر الآن.
(Her clothes already)
(ملابسها جاهزة)
(carry the agarwood scent.)
(تحمل رائحة العود.)
(If she stays more...)
(إذا بقيت لفترة أطول...)
You're back.
لقد عدت.
My lady.
سيدتي.
The weather is dry.
الطقس جاف.
You've even got chapped lips.
حتى شفتيك متشققتان.
Have some water.
اشرب بعض الماء.
Stop nagging.
توقف عن التذمر.
Why are you dressing your wound here?
لماذا تقوم بتضميد جرحك هنا؟
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
I've been waiting
لقد كنت أنتظر
for you all day.
لك طوال اليوم.
I've treated the wound on my arm.
لقد عالجت الجرح الموجود على ذراعي.
But my lady,
لكن يا سيدتي،
here.
هنا.
What should I do
ماذا علي أن أفعل
about the wound on my shoulder blade
بخصوص الجرح الموجود على لوح كتفي
without your help?
بدون مساعدتك؟
No need to change the dressing
لا داعي لتغيير الضمادة
as often in this dry weather.
كما هو الحال في هذا الطقس الجاف.
I treat you wholeheartedly.
أعاملك بكل إخلاص.
But you play mind games with me.
لكنك تلعب معي ألعاباً نفسية.
If you were to cast me aside,
لو أنك نبذتني جانباً،
I might as well die.
ربما من الأفضل لي أن أموت.
No, no.
لا لا.
Fine, I'll do it.
حسناً، سأفعل ذلك.
Stop howling.
توقف عن العواء.
You smell so nice.
رائحتك جميلة جداً.
Do me a favor, my lady.
يا سيدتي، أسدي لي معروفاً.
Don't use Xie Fei's medicine.
لا تستخدم دواء شي فاي.
It hurts too much. I can't bear it.
الأمر مؤلم للغاية. لا أستطيع تحمله.
So it hurts, huh?
إذن الأمر مؤلم، أليس كذلك؟
Still running that mouth?
ما زلت تتحدث بهذه الطريقة؟
Save your energy for healing.
وفر طاقتك للشفاء.
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
You're still here?
ما زلت هنا؟
I was concerned
كنت قلقاً
that some scoundrel might disturb you.
قد يزعجك بعض الأوغاد.
So I came to check on you.
لذا جئت لأطمئن عليك.
Grand Tutor Xie
المعلم الكبير شي
shared a bed with me just days ago.
لقد شاركت السرير معي قبل أيام قليلة.
Everyone in the Chen State knows.
الجميع في ولاية تشين يعلمون ذلك.
And now,
والآن،
he's changing my dressing in person.
إنه يغير ملابسي بنفسه.
Is he really obsessed with me?
هل هو مهووس بي حقاً؟
Are you really obsessed with me?
هل أنت مهووس بي حقاً؟
Done.
منتهي.
My lady.
سيدتي.
You just sat there and watched him
جلست هناك وراقبته فقط
bully me?
هل تتنمر علي؟
You are the Seventeenth Prince of Qi.
أنت الأمير السابع عشر لـ "تشي".
If you weren't practically begging to be bullied,
لو لم تكن تتوسل عمليًا للتعرض للتنمر،
who would dare bully you?
من يجرؤ على التنمر عليك؟
What is this?
ما هذا؟
I've never seen it.
لم أره من قبل.
Xuzhou pastries.
معجنات شوتشو.
I tasted them once when I practiced martial arts as a kid.
لقد تذوقتها مرة واحدة عندما كنت أمارس فنون الدفاع عن النفس وأنا طفل.
Your master bought them for you?
هل اشتراها لك سيدك؟
See if it tastes the same.
جرب أن تتأكد من أن طعمه هو نفسه.
I haven't had one
لم أحصل على واحدة
for so many years.
لسنوات عديدة.
I'm from the Qi State.
أنا من ولاية تشي.
My lady,
سيدتي،
I've never tasted them.
لم أتذوقها قط.
Makes sense.
هذا منطقي.
Qi pastries must differ from ours.
لا بد أن معجنات تشي تختلف عن معجناتنا.
Try it.
جربها.
Don't you have hands?
أليس لديك أيدٍ؟
My lady, it's so sweet.
يا سيدتي، إنه لأمر لطيف للغاية.
Tea from Jigu Mountain in Jiangcheng?
الشاي من جبل Jigu في Jiangcheng؟
Yes.
نعم.
It's the only pouch of new tea.
إنها العبوة الوحيدة من الشاي الجديد.
I kept it with me,
احتفظت به معي.
hoping to give it to you myself
أتمنى أن أقدمها لك بنفسي
when I see you.
عندما أراك.
You remember that I love new teas from different places.
أتذكر أنني أحب أنواع الشاي الجديدة من أماكن مختلفة؟
He's so thoughtful.
إنه شخص مراعٍ للغاية.
Although he only brought a pouch of tea,
على الرغم من أنه لم يحضر سوى كيس شاي،
it's enough
هذا يكفي
for me to share with you.
لأشاركها معكم.
(Xie Fei.)
(شيه فاي.)
(You despicable man.)
(يا لك من رجل حقير.)
But the jade hairpin is taking a long time to polish.
لكن تلميع دبوس الشعر المصنوع من اليشم يستغرق وقتاً طويلاً.
I wanted
أردت
to carve it meticulously.
لنحتها بدقة متناهية.
You'll outshine
ستتفوق على الجميع
the spring with it.
ومعها الربيع.
Spring's beauty
جمال الربيع
pales before our love.
يتضاءل كل شيء أمام حبنا.
Spring fades. But you must not.
الربيع يتلاشى. لكن لا يجب عليك ذلك.
(Oh, no.)
(أوه، لا.)
(My lady has fallen for a scoundrel.)
(لقد وقعت سيدتي في غرام وغد.)
It's getting late.
لقد تأخر الوقت.
I'll leave now.
سأغادر الآن.
Tomorrow, I'll guide Zhuozhou officials
غدًا، سأقوم بتوجيه مسؤولي مدينة تشوتشو
to discover the gunpowder.
لاكتشاف البارود.
Chancellor Huo will surely panic
من المؤكد أن المستشار هو سيصاب بالذعر
and check on the gunpowder in the capital.
وتحقق من وجود البارود في العاصمة.
We'll catch him in the act.
سنقبض عليه متلبساً بالجرم.
Be careful.
احرص.
Stay safe.
ابقَ آمناً.
The matter is grave.
الأمر خطير.
I'll take Feng Wuhen with me.
سآخذ فنغ ووهين معي.
He's staying by your side,
سيبقى بجانبك،
clearly up to no good.
من الواضح أنه يخطط لشيء سيء.
It's a precaution.
إنه إجراء احترازي.
(Who gave you the right)
(من أعطاك الحق؟)
(to speak ill of me?)
(أن يتحدثوا عني بسوء؟)
They found those spots?
هل عثروا على تلك البقع؟
Seven out of thirteen.
سبعة من أصل ثلاثة عشر.
Caught you.
أمسكت بك.
Move them.
انقلهم.
The hounds
الكلاب
chase the blood scent relentlessly,
تعقب رائحة الدم بلا هوادة،
unaware they're charging blindly towards a cliff.
غير مدركين أنهم يندفعون بشكل أعمى نحو جرف.
Time to end the game.
حان وقت إنهاء اللعبة.
It's fishy.
الأمر مريب.
Take a look.
ألقِ نظرة.
Understood.
مفهوم.
Alert the Zhuozhou authorities.
أبلغوا سلطات تشوتشو.
♪The wind rises, snow falls♪
♪تهب الرياح، ويتساقط الثلج♪
♪To stain endless remorse with red♪
♪لتلطيخ الندم الذي لا ينتهي باللون الأحمر♪
♪No regrets in moves made. Let the game unfold♪
لا ندم على الخطوات التي اتخذتها. دع اللعبة تتكشف.
♪Sorrow and joy intertwined♪
♪الحزن والفرح متشابكان♪
♪Yet we can't escape karma♪
♪لكننا لا نستطيع الهروب من الكارما♪
♪Lament this fleeting life♪
♪رثوا هذه الحياة الزائلة♪
♪So elusive♪
♪مراوغ للغاية♪
♪So indistinct♪
♪غير واضح للغاية♪
♪Resent farewells♪
♪وداعات حزينة♪
♪Remembering each other♪
♪نتذكر بعضنا البعض♪
♪Love can't be extinguished♪
♪الحب لا ينطفئ♪
♪Unwilling to accept♪
♪غير راغب في القبول♪
♪Rewriting the story♪
♪إعادة كتابة القصة♪
♪And praying♪
♪والصلاة♪
♪A long-cherished wish♪
أمنية طالما تمنيتها
♪In a daze♪
♪في حالة ذهول♪
♪Suddenly it's those years again♪
♪فجأة تعود تلك السنوات من جديد♪
♪How I wish to relive my old dreams♪
♪كم أتمنى أن أعيش أحلامي القديمة من جديد♪
♪Rewrite those torn pages♪
♪أعد كتابة تلك الصفحات الممزقة♪